<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tracks on MXRaceHub - Ultimate Supercross and Motocross Platform</title>
    <link>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tracks on MXRaceHub - Ultimate Supercross and Motocross Platform</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>team@mxracehub.com (MXRaceHub Team)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>team@mxracehub.com (MXRaceHub Team)</webMaster>
    <copyright>© 2025 MXRaceHub Team</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://mxracehub.site/tracks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Angel Stadium of Anaheim</title>
      <link>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/angel-stadium/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/angel-stadium/</guid>
      <description>The Traditional Season Opener # Angel Stadium of Anaheim, affectionately known as &amp;ldquo;A1&amp;rdquo; in the racing community, holds a special place in Supercross history as the traditional season-opening venue. Since 1976, this baseball stadium has been transformed into a battleground for the world&amp;rsquo;s best Supercross riders, with only rare exceptions when the series opener was held elsewhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T Stadium</title>
      <link>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/at-t-stadium/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/at-t-stadium/</guid>
      <description>The Spectacle of Supercross in America&amp;rsquo;s Stadium # AT&amp;amp;T Stadium, home of the NFL&amp;rsquo;s Dallas Cowboys, stands as one of the most impressive venues on the AMA Supercross calendar. Opened in 2009 and hosting its first Supercross event in 2010, &amp;ldquo;Jerry World&amp;rdquo; (nicknamed after Cowboys owner Jerry Jones) offers an unparalleled combination of size, amenities, and atmosphere for motorcycle racing events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daytona International Speedway</title>
      <link>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/daytona-international-speedway/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/daytona-international-speedway/</guid>
      <description>The Most Unique Race on the Supercross Calendar # Daytona International Speedway hosts what is widely considered the most distinctive and challenging event on the Supercross calendar. Unlike traditional stadium supercross tracks, the Daytona course is built on the infield of the famous NASCAR speedway, resulting in a hybrid that combines elements of both supercross and motocross.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ford Field</title>
      <link>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/detroit-supercross/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/detroit-supercross/</guid>
      <description>Venue Type Domed Football Stadium Capacity 65,000 Surface Dirt (imported for Supercross events) First Supercross 2006 Notable Feature Dome stadium that protects from harsh Michigan winter weather Venue Overview Ford Field is home to the NFL&#39;s Detroit Lions and has been a staple on the Monster Energy Supercross calendar since 2006.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox Raceway at Pala</title>
      <link>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/fox-raceway/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/fox-raceway/</guid>
      <description>Southern California&amp;rsquo;s Premier Motocross Facility # Fox Raceway at Pala, located in the rolling hills of Northern San Diego County, has established itself as one of Southern California&amp;rsquo;s premier motocross destinations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High Point Raceway</title>
      <link>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/high-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/high-point/</guid>
      <description>The Rolling Hills of Pennsylvania # High Point Raceway has been a staple of American motocross since it first appeared on the AMA Pro Motocross Championship schedule in 1977. Nestled in the rolling hills of southwestern Pennsylvania near the West Virginia border, this iconic track is known for its distinctive red clay surface, dramatic elevation changes, and rich racing history spanning over four decades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MetLife Stadium</title>
      <link>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/metlife-stadium/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/metlife-stadium/</guid>
      <description>The East Coast Supercross Showcase # MetLife Stadium stands as the premier East Coast venue for Monster Energy AMA Supercross, bringing the excitement of professional motorcycle racing to the shadows of New York City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raymond James Stadium</title>
      <link>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/raymond-james-stadium/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/raymond-james-stadium/</guid>
      <description>Stadium Overview # Raymond James Stadium, affectionately known as &amp;ldquo;Ray Jay&amp;rdquo; by locals, serves as one of the premier venues on the Monster Energy AMA Supercross circuit. Home to the NFL&amp;rsquo;s Tampa Bay Buccaneers, this impressive facility transforms into a world-class Supercross battleground each season, challenging riders with its unique Florida conditions and typically technical track designs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RedBud MX</title>
      <link>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/redbud/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/redbud/</guid>
      <description>America&amp;rsquo;s Motocross Track # RedBud MX is widely considered the crown jewel of American motocross tracks. Located in the rolling hills of southwestern Michigan, this iconic facility hosts what many consider to be the most patriotic and energetic round of the AMA Pro Motocross Championship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rice-Eccles Stadium</title>
      <link>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/rice-eccles-stadium/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/rice-eccles-stadium/</guid>
      <description>The High-Altitude Season Finale # Rice-Eccles Stadium, home to the University of Utah Utes football team, has established itself as one of the most challenging venues on the AMA Supercross calendar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snapdragon Stadium</title>
      <link>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/san-diego-snapdragon-stadium/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/san-diego-snapdragon-stadium/</guid>
      <description>The New Home of San Diego Supercross # Snapdragon Stadium represents the newest chapter in San Diego&amp;rsquo;s long and storied Supercross history. Opened in 2022, this state-of-the-art facility has taken over from the historic Qualcomm/Jack Murphy Stadium (demolished in 2021) as Southern California&amp;rsquo;s premier Supercross venue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snapdragon Stadium</title>
      <link>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/snapdragon-stadium/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/snapdragon-stadium/</guid>
      <description>Venue Type Football Stadium Capacity 35,000 Surface Dirt (imported for Supercross events) First Supercross 2023 Notable Feature Brand new facility replacing Qualcomm/PETCO Park as San Diego&#39;s Supercross venue Venue Overview Snapdragon Stadium is a state-of-the-art venue that opened in 2022 as the home of San Diego State University&#39;s football team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unadilla MX</title>
      <link>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/unadilla-mx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/unadilla-mx/</guid>
      <description>The Historic Battleground # Unadilla MX represents the living history of American motocross. Nestled in the rolling hills of central New York state, this legendary venue has been hosting world-class motocross events since 1969, making it one of the oldest continuously operating professional motocross facilities in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washougal MX Park</title>
      <link>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/washougal-mx-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mxracehub.site/tracks/washougal-mx-park/</guid>
      <description>The Cathedral of Motocross # Washougal MX Park stands as one of the most visually stunning and technically challenging venues in American motocross. Nestled in the lush forests of the Pacific Northwest along the Columbia River, this iconic track has earned the nickname &amp;ldquo;The Cathedral of Motocross&amp;rdquo; for its breathtaking natural setting and the almost religious reverence it inspires among riders and fans alike.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>